This is a work of fiction.
Underage drinking is strongly prohibited and illegal.
Scenes involving alcohol with forceful consumption
and shameful acts are not encouraged.
Please view this as a comedy.
Furthermore, all characters appearing
in this work are of legal age.
（チャイム）
The make-up exam is now over.
（講師）
それでは 追試を終わります
We're done! We're done!
（伊織(いおり)）
あー 終わった 終わった
I don't think I failed.
（耕平(こうへい)）
どうにか赤点は免れそうだ
Kitahara, Imamura...
（山本(やまもと)）北原(きたはら) 今村(いまむら)
Do you want to go for a drink?
（野島(のじま)）これから乾杯とかどうよ？
Yeah. Nice.
（伊織）おっ いいな
（耕平）かまわんぞ
Sure, I'll go.
All right! Let's go to your place, Kitahara.
よっしゃ　じゃ 北原の家な
Yeah, at Kitahara's place.
そうだな 北原の家へ行くか
Got it. Kitahara's place.
（藤原(ふじわら)）分かった 北原の家だな
Okay. I'll take you guys there.
（耕平）ＯＫ 案内しよう
Wait, there's something wrong here.
（伊織）
いや その流れはおかしい
What is it, Kitahara?
（御手洗(みたらい)）なんだ 北原
Why does it have to be at my place?
なんで俺の家なんだよ！
It's obvious.
そりゃ 決まってるだろ
It's because there's something we want to check.
確認しておくべきことがあるからだ
-Check?
-Yeah.
確認？
ほら 前に
今村が言ってただろう
Imamura said so before, right?
We're not dating or anything!
別に つきあっているわけでも
ないんだ
But you live together.
一緒に暮らしてるがな
Hey, Kitahara.
（野島）なあ 北原君
It's not true, right?
（山本）まさかとは思うけど
You're not really living with Kotegawa, right?
（野島･山本）
本当に 古手川(こてがわ)さんと―
一緒に暮らしてたり
しないよね
（伊織）
バレたら確実に殺(や)られる…
If they find out, they'll kill me!
Wait, they already think I'm dating Chisa.
いや つきあっていることに
なってる千紗はまだいい
The real problem is...
それより問題は…
If they found out I live with a beautiful,
hot girl like her...
あんな美人で スタイルのいい
お姉さんと―
一緒に暮らしてると バレたら…
何をされるか…
頼む 耕平！　助けてくれ！
I can't imagine what they'd do to me.
I beg you, Kohei! Help me!
（耕平）フフ…
（伊織）このゲス野郎！
You scumbag!
Be passionate, my friends
♪～
Shine bright with the sun
Dive into the blue sky
And let summer take it all
GRAND BLUE DREAMING
Be passionate, my friends
Shine bright with the sun
Dive into the blue sky
And let summer take it all
An expanding ocean of possibilities
Summer is our amore
We'll swear to the crystal clear sky
Summer is in our hands
Be passionate, my friends
Shine bright with the sun
Dive into the blue sky
And let summer take it all
With a cheerful heart
Don't mess with me
Keep going even if you fall
And let summer take it all
～♪
This work is an original copyrighted material
of the Content Provider. Unauthorized reproduction
or distribution of this work in any form or manner
is prohibited. Some viewers might find this work disturbing
as it may contain strong language, a degree of violence
or adult situations. Viewer discretion is advised.
Please watch it at your own risk.
（ドアが開く音）
（走る足音）
The story, names, characters and incidents portrayed
in this work are fictitious. No identification with actual
persons, organizations, religions, places and products
is intended. The Content Provider, the producers
and related parties shall have no liability,
as to the accuracy, legality, safety or suitability
for any purpose of the information provided in this work.
The views and opinions expressed herein do not reflect
the views and opinions of the Content Provider,
or any of its affiliates, partners, subsidiaries, or Licensee.
（伊織の荒い息遣い）
（奈々華(ななか)）おかえりなさい 伊織君
Welcome back, Iori.
Nanaka!
（伊織）奈々華さん！
（奈々華）どうしたの？
What's wrong?
今日 大学の連中が
俺の部屋に来ると言ってまして
The guys from college said they're coming over today.
Wow, your friends are coming over.
へえ お友達が来るのね
Please hide somewhere right now!
（伊織）なので 大至急
隠れてください！
What? Why?
え？　どうして？
It's hard to explain.
To tell you the truth...
（伊織）うまく
説明できないんですが
ありていに言うと―
my life is at stake.
俺の命に関わるんです
But I thought they were your friends.
（奈々華）
来るのはお友達じゃないの？
（一同）うーっす
Hey.
I brought some drinks and snacks.
飲み物と食い物
買ってきたぞ
Oh, thanks.
おお… お疲れ
A diving shop?
ダイビングショップ？
So this is where you're staying.
ここが北原の下宿先か
It's a nice store.
（御手洗）きれいな店だな
It's normally filled with dirty naked guys though.
いつもは 汚い裸だらけだがな
いや 俺は離れの部屋なんだ
さあ 行こうぜ
Well, my room is detached.
Hey. Let's go.
-What's the big idea?
-I want to look around.
（野島）なんだよ
（藤原）もうちょっと見せろよ
いいから いいから
Don't worry.
I can hide Chisa and Nanaka this way.
（伊織）これで 千紗と
奈々華さんの存在は隠せる
Well, here is my room.
んで ここが俺の部屋な
あ？
Kitahara!
（御手洗･野島）北原くーん！
Azusa!
（伊織）梓(あずさ)さーん！
You bastard! I'm so jealous!
貴様 なんて羨ましい生活を！
I'll never forgive you!
絶対に許さんぞ！
あ… これは違うんだ！
It's not what you think!
Hey. Calm down, you guys.
（山本）おいおい
落ち着けよ お前ら
Yamamoto?
（野島）や… 山本？
Are you going to forgive this traitor?
（藤原）お前
この裏切りを許すのか？
He didn't betray us.
裏切りも何も
帽子ぐらいで騒ぐこともあるまい
Don't get so worked up over a hat.
-A hat?
-Are you going to put it on?
（伊織）帽子!?
（耕平）かぶる気か!?
He's so jealous he's lost touch with reality.
（野島）こいつ 羨ましすぎて
現実が見えなくなっている!?
What's this?
（御手洗）ん？　これは？
（伊織）んっ!?
Iori!
（野島）伊織くーん！
Cakey!
（伊織）ケバ子ー！
（山本）座薬か…
（耕平）なぜ そう見える!?
Is it a suppository?
Does it look like one?
（野島）お前 もう頭が…
Have you gone crazy?
It's Kitahara's fault!
北原のせいだぞ！
（伊織）俺が悪いのか!?
What did I do wrong?
This is-- Our club used it for a game.
これは その…
サークルの遊びで使った物なんだ
（野島）ん？
（山本）そうなのか
Really?
It's not Kotegawa's size.
（藤原）そういえば 古手川さんの
サイズには合わないか 巨大だ
-It's huge.
-Now that you mention it... Yeah. It's huge.
（山本）言われてみれば
そうだな　巨大だな
There's no way it's real in the first place.
考えてみりゃ
そもそも本物なわけねえや
If it is real, whoever took it off
couldn't have gone home.
もし 本物だとしたら
脱いだ人は 帰り困るもんなあ
Girls don't go home without their bras, right?
ノーブラで帰るなんて
普通 しないだろ
Well, she's not normal...
（伊織）あの人
普通じゃないから…
まあ ほかに
怪しいものは特に… ん？
Well, there's nothing else suspicious here.
I must be mistaken...
いやいやいや
何かの見間違いかと… ん？
イヤ～！
（伊織）ん？
（耕平）どうした お前ら
What's wrong, you guys?
（野島）いやいやいや！
（藤原）なんでもないんだ
No! It's nothing.
This guy has weird stuff.
こいつの持ち物
絶対おかしいだろ…
I get the feeling he's dangerous.
女の影どころか
ヤバい闇が潜んでやがる
Let's just pretend we didn't notice.
とりあえず 気付いてない
フリをしようぜ
お？
FROM WORKS
Are you trying to find a job?
バイト 探してるのか？
Trying to save up for something?
何か 欲しいものでも？
ダイビングって 金がかかってさ
Diving costs a lot of money.
（野島）えっ…
EVENT COMPANION
（４人）ああ…
Is he--?
まさか あいつ！
Let's just drink.
と… とりあえず飲もうぜ
Yeah. Let's drink and forget it.
そ… そうだな
酒飲んで忘れよう
I'm too scared to think about it.
深く考えると怖いからな…
（伊織）ん？
（耕平）なんの話だ？
What are you talking about?
（野島）それじゃ無事
追試突破ということで
Congratulations for passing our make-up exam!
Cheers!
（一同）カンパーイ！
プハーッ！
Beer gets bitter after a little while.
ぶっちゃけ ビールって
後半苦くないか？
分かる 分かる
I know!
（伊織）海から上がったあとの
一口目はすごいけどな
The first sip after diving tastes great.
（伊織）海から上がったあとの
一口目はすごいけどな
（ふすまが開く音）
You're right.
（耕平）確かに
（伊織）ん？
What's wrong, Yamamoto?
（伊織）どうした？　山本
You were in the bathroom for a long time.
（耕平）やけに
長いトイレだったな
Hey, Kitahara.
なあ 北原…
What?
な… なんだ？
ハァ…
（伊織）ん？
I met an angel...
（山本）
俺 天使に出会っちまったよ…
（伊織）ファーッ！
She's beautiful!
（御手洗）すげえ美人だな おい
（野島）どこで見たんだ？
Where did you see her?
I went outside for some fresh air,
and there she was.
（山本）さっき 酔い覚ましに
外に出たら 偶然 海で
Seriously?
マジか！
When I saw her just now, I thought...
俺 さっき彼女を見かけて
思ったんだよ
お… おう
What did you think?
何を思ったんだ？
I want to date her.
（山本）この人と
つきあいたいって
（野島）はあ？
（藤原）そりゃ無理じゃないか？
-What?
-That's impossible.
You're not a good match.
分不相応すぎるだろ
I know that. But... But...
分かってる
でも でも…
それが無理なら
俺の子を産んでもらいたいんだ
If that's impossible, then I want her to have my children.
This guy's an idiot.
おっと こいつ
結構なアホだぞ
I'm embarrassed to admit I know him.
知り合いであることを
恥じるレベルだ
-We're similar enough.
-You too...?
（耕平）類友か
（御手洗）お前もな
Where are you going?
（伊織）どこへ行く？
（耕平）終電か？
Taking the last train?
（山本）さっきの天使を捜しに行く
I'm going to look for that angel.
What?
（伊織）なに？
（耕平）一体 何をしに？
What are you going to do?
It's obvious, isn't it?
（山本）決まってるだろう…
I will kneel down and beg her to be with me!
彼女になってくれるよう
土下座しに！
Is that how you tell a girl how you feel?
（伊織）告白の
基本姿勢が土下座なのか
Now I'm curious about your past.
（耕平）今までの
遍歴が気になるところだ
（山本）戻ってきたとき
俺は一人前の男だ！
When I come back, I'll be a man!
お… おう　そうか
Oh, really...?
A man, huh?
一人前の男ねえ…
Well, good luck.
まあ 頑張れよ
What do you think will happen?
（耕平）で どうなると思う？
（御手洗）相手が
あんな美人だとなあ…
Well, she's beautiful, so...
He'll get rejected on the spot and cry.
（野島）即座にフラれて
男泣きってところじゃないか
I was thinking the same.
（藤原）なんだ 同じ意見か
We shouldn't make bets on this.
（耕平）賭けが成立しないな
（一同）お？
（泣き声）
Wait. What happened?
（一同）いや 待て
何があったんだ…
おい 北原！
あれはなんなんだよ！
Hey, Kitahara!
What's going on?
What's going on with you?
まずはお前がなんなんだ
Can't you tell by looking?
見て分からないのかよ！
-Can you tell?
-No idea.
（耕平）分かるか？
（野島）分かってたまるか
I was going over to the beach just now.
俺 さっき
海に行こうとしたんだよ
But then I ran into a bunch of naked guys.
そしたら 途中で
大勢の裸の男たちに出会って…
Okay. I understand now.
（耕平･伊織）ＯＫ 理解した
（野島）えっ!?
What do you mean you understand now?
（御手洗）
なぜ それだけで分かる？
Not sure. But it must have been horrible!
よく分からんが
そりゃあ災難だったな
Seeing naked guys just makes my eyes rot.
男の裸なんて
目が腐るだけだもんなあ
We see that every day.
（伊織）俺たちは
毎日 見てるがなあ…
Have some more to drink.
まあ 飲め飲め
You were going to get rejected anyway.
どうせ
フラれる運命だったんだよ
Drink up and forget it!
飲んで忘れろ！
You'll never get a girlfriend.
お前に彼女なんて
ありえねえよ
Can't you guys comfort me a little?
お前ら 少しは慰めるとか
できないわけ？
Anyway, we checked it out.
It appears Kitahara doesn't live with Kotegawa.
しかし まあ
こうして確認してみると―
北原の同棲説はデマっぽいな
（藤原）んだな
Yeah.
（山本）まったく
今村も冗談キツいぜ
You tell bad jokes, Imamura.
No, I wasn't joking--
いや 俺は冗談なんか…
グハッ！
Kohei likes telling jokes.
耕平は冗談が好きだからな
I'm not even sure they're dating in the first place.
そもそも つきあっていること
自体が怪しいだろう
I was thinking the same.
それ 俺も思ってた
It'd be weird if he had a girlfriend.
こいつに彼女なんて
不自然すぎる
You guys don't know anything about me.
（伊織）
お前らに俺の何が分かる
大体 あんなかわいい子が…
A cute girl wouldn't--
Iori, I'm out of the shower.
You can take one--
（千紗(ちさ)）伊織
お風呂あいたから 次…
（千紗）あ…
（野島たち）は？
あっ ご… ごめん
友達が来てると思わなくて
Sorry! I didn't know your friends were over.
（ぶつかる音）
（千紗）いっ…
（野島たち）ん…
Kitahara!
（野島たち）北原くーん！
No! Listen to me--
（伊織）違うんだ！
俺の話を…
Kohei, help me!
耕平！　たす 助け…
Don't get blood on the floor.
（耕平）お前ら
血で床を汚すなよ
You bastard!
（伊織）貴様～！
Hey, Chisa.
（伊織）なあ 千紗…
（千紗）何？
What?
Don't you feel sorry for me when you see me like this?
俺の この姿見て
かわいそうとか思わないか？
Sorry.
（千紗）ごめん…
（奈々華）本当に命に関わってる
His life really was at stake...
Wow, the ocean's so beautiful here! I want to go!
（愛菜(あいな)）わっ ここの海 きれい！
行ってみたい！
Miyakojima, huh?
宮古島(みやこじま)かあ
I want to go there.
こんな景色 見てみたいな
I want to go diving there.
俺は ここに潜ってみたい
（千紗･愛菜）うう…
Are you talking about diving?
（時田(ときた)）おっ ダイビングの話か？
あっ 先輩！
私 早くライセンス取って―
Tokita! I want to get my license soon
and go diving in lots of places!
いろいろ潜ってみたいです！
（時田）ハハハ　そうかそうか
I see, I see.
It's great that you're passionate about club activities.
（寿(ことぶき)）サークル活動に
熱心なのは いいことだ
What are we doing today?
で 今日は何するんです？
言われたとおり
動きやすい服を持ってきましたが
I brought loose clothes, like you said.
We're going to have a doubles tennis match.
（２人）テニスで
ダブルスの試合を行う
Hold on!
（耕平･伊織）ちょい待てや！
It's training for the buddy system.
（時田）これは
バディ･システムの訓練
That's not true, right?
（伊織）
いや 違いますよね
フッ… 実は 賞金目的だ
Actually, we're after the prize money.
Tinkerbell's captain had an idea.
ティンベルの会長から
打診があってな
If we lose, we'll give you the second-place prize money
from the women's and men's pageants.
（工藤(くどう)）負けたら ミスコン･男コン
２位の賞金を譲渡するよ
Tinkerbell? You mean--?
ティンベルって あの!?
We can't beat the tennis club at tennis!
テニサーにテニスで
勝てるわけないでしょうに
（伊織）ていうか
絶対に仕返し目的ですよね
They're trying to get revenge.
They're trying to humiliate us.
（耕平）俺たちに
恥をかかせようって…
（時田）ああ それは分かる
（伊織）だったら！
-Yeah. I know.
-Then why?
We concluded that...
（寿）だが 俺たちはこう思うんだ
Your humiliation is a small price to pay
for the prize money.
（２人）お前らの恥で
賞金が手に入るなら安いものだと
（伊織･耕平）そりゃ
あんたらは関係ないからな！
That's because you don't have anything on the line!
（部員たちの声援）
Hit it!
Those guys think they're watching a baseball game.
（伊織）あの人たちは 野球観戦か
何かと勘違いしていないか？
They don't even know the rules.
（耕平）ルールも
誤解してるようだしな
Aren't you guys going to join in?
（愛菜）お２人は出ないんですか？
I'll cheer them on from here.
（梓）私はここから
応援してるよん
I'll do my best to cheer them on too.
私も一生懸命 応援するわね
You're wearing sweats.
そういや お前
ジャージなんだな
Why not wear tennis clothes?
（耕平）
テニスウエア 着ないのか？
I'd feel embarrassed exposing my legs.
着ないわよ
脚出すの 恥ずかしいし
But you wore them at the beauty pageant.
（伊織）だが
ミスコンのときは着ていたろ
I was wearing makeup.
（愛菜）あれは 化粧してたし
酔った勢いもあったからで
And I was drunk.
What does "makeup" mean to you?
（耕平）お前にとって
化粧ってなんなんだ
And...
それに あの２人の近くで
そんな格好する自信ないわよ
I don't have the confidence to dress like that
next to those two.
（伊織･耕平）ああ…
Well, sweats are what suit us.
まあ 俺たちには
ジャージがお似合いだよな
Yeah. We'd just stand out in tennis clothes.
そうそう テニスウエアなんて
着ても浮いちゃうし
We're amateurs at tennis anyway.
テニスなんて素人だからな
WOMEN'S LOCKER ROOM
CHISA-CHAN PREPARED
（千紗）えっ ええ…
Today, as we agreed upon,
（工藤）
じゃあ 今回は約束どおり―
we're going to have a doubles match with three sets.
ダブルスの１セットマッチを
３試合で
-Okay.
-I'm lost, but I'm fine with that.
（時田）おう！
（寿）よく分からんがそれでいいぞ
You're not dressed like a girl today.
今回は 女装していないんだね
Neither are you.
（伊織）お前もな
（工藤）俺はもともとしてねえよ！
I never did!
あれ？　そっちの子は新人？
Is she new?
Yes.
そうですね
He thinks they've never met before.
あいつ 初対面だと思われてるぞ
（耕平）あの化粧は 外敵から
身を守るものだったのか
Her makeup is like armor protecting her from enemies.
（耕平）あの化粧は 外敵から
身を守るものだったのか
（工藤）今度
うちに来ない？
（耕平）あの化粧は 外敵から
身を守るものだったのか
ミスコンの子も一緒に
アハハハ…
Let the first game begin.
（審判）
それでは第１試合 始めます
Tokita! Kotobuki! You can do it!
（愛菜）時田先輩 寿先輩
頑張って～！
-Okay.
-I'm going to do my best!
（時田）おお！
（寿）頑張るぞ～！
Okay. One, two...
（時田）んじゃ せーの
うりゃあ！
Fifteen-love!
（審判）フィフティーン･ラブ
（工藤）ああ…
What was that just now?
（部員）な… なんだ今の
What's up with that serve?
（部員）なあに
あんな力任せのサーブ―
You won't get away that easily next time.
もう やすやすと入らないさ
あーい！
（部員）ぐっ！
（時田）行ったぞ 寿！
-Nice, Kotobuki!
-Leave it to me!
（寿）よっしゃ 任せろ！
（部員）しまった！
No!
（寿）おーら！
Take that!
Thirty-love!
（審判）サーティー･ラブ
おお いいっぽいぞ
Nice.
Tokita! Kotobuki!
（愛菜）キャー！
時田先輩！　寿先輩！
They'll be fine.
大丈夫そうですね
They're really good at sports.
まあ 運動神経は
桁違いだからね
フッ…
Where are the others?
あれ？　そういえば
ほかの先輩方は？
They were there just now.
さっきまでそこに…
Maybe they drank too much.
（梓）飲みすぎて
潰れてるのかなあ
I'll go check on them.
ちょっと 様子見てきます
（梓）よろしく～
Thanks.
What is this?
（伊織）こ…
（耕平）これは！
They really are drunk.
（伊織）マジで
酔いつぶれているとは…
What's going on?
（耕平）どうなっているんだ
Oh, Iori and Kohei!
（東(あずま)）おお！　伊織と耕平か
（伊織）先輩！
Hey!
これは一体 どういうことです
What's going on?
Tinkerbell brought us some drinks...
ティンベルが飲み物を
差し入れてくれてな
and we drank too much.
つい 飲みすぎて…
There's still booze left?
まだ酒が余っている？
バカな この程度で先輩方が…
They hardly drank any of it.
It evaporated in a flash!
（耕平）一瞬で蒸発!?
What did they make them drink?
一体 何を飲まされたんだ!?
Let's cheer them on by ourselves.
（伊織）というわけで―
俺たちだけで応援しましょう
（梓）オッケー
（伊織）それで
試合はどんな感じです？
How is the match going?
Well...
（奈々華）それが…
（寿･時田）とっとっと…
（寿）ハッハッハ…
He's not moving around so well anymore.
なんだか 妙に
動きが悪くなって
Those two drank in secret.
（耕平･伊織）あの２人
隠れて飲んでやがったな
（ホイッスル）
At this rate, we'll lose.
このままだと負けるかもよ
I thought they'd be able to win.
あの２人なら
勝てると思ったんだけどねえ
Kitahara, is there any way to sober them up?
北原 あの２人の
酔いを覚ます方法はないか？
うーむ こうしよう
I've got an idea.
Court change!
（審判）コートチェンジ
（部員たち）フゥー
This is easy.
（部員）こりゃ 余裕だな
（部員）ああ
Yeah!
（２人）ブハーッ！
（部員）な… なんだ これ！
What's this?
There's something different inside.
（部員）中身が変わってないか？
（ホイッスル）
Won by Peek-a-Boo!
ウォンバイ Peek a Boo(ピーカブー)
（寿･時田）ん？
What did you do?
（千紗）なんかやったの？
（伊織）逆転の発想だ
Our comeback strategy.
Instead of getting our team sober,
we're going to get them drunk.
こちらを覚ますんじゃなく
向こうも酔わせればいい
スポーツマンシップは!?
What about sportsmanship?
ぐう…
We won one match.
とにかく これで１勝だ
お前らで決めてきてくれ
It's your turn.
-Off you go.
-Okay.
いってらっしゃい
（愛菜）はあい…
By the way, where are my sweats?
ところでお姉ちゃん
私のジャージは？
They're at home.
家にあるわよ
（千紗）え…
I don't feel good about this.
（愛菜）自信ないなあ…
Kotegawa, are you good at tennis?
古手川さん テニスは？
（千紗）少し
Kind of.
（部員）あら～
Hello there
You're from the beauty pageant.
（部員）あなた ミスコンの
あっ ミスコン２位の…
I got second place.
You're Kotegawa!
You won by having your skirt flipped up!
スカートめくりで優勝した
古手川さんじゃない！
（千紗）うっ！
（部員）残念ね
Too bad. Being sexy won't work on us.
今回はお色気が効かない相手で
Stick to flipping your skirt for the audience.
（部員）今日はせいぜい―
ギャラリーに愛想と
アンスコでも振りまくことね
（部員たち）キャハハハ！
Kotegawa?
こ… 古手川さん？
Game play!
（審判）ゲームプレイ
（千紗）ううっ！
（部員）ふっ！
（愛菜）んっ！
（部員）ああっ！
This is a real match, unlike just a little while ago.
へえ… さっきと違って―
ちゃんと試合になってますね
（時田）失礼な！
-How rude!
-We played hard too.
（寿）俺たちも
ちゃんとやってただろ
Yeah, yeah. Drink some water.
はいはい いいから水飲んで
Do your best, you two!
２人とも頑張って！
（千紗）ふっ！
Chisa's really into it.
千紗のやつ 妙にやる気出してるな
You!
（部員）このっ！
（愛菜）あっ！
ふっ！
（一同）おおっ！
（時田）見事なカバーだったな
Nice cover!
You two are good friends.
２人とも
いいバディ関係ね
（愛菜）イエイ！
（伊織）じゃ 声出しましょうか
Let's do a cheer!
Repeat after me.
俺に続いてください
千紗！　ナイスバディ！
Chisa, nice buddy!
Nice buddy, Kotegawa!
ナイスバディ 古手川！
Nice buddy, Chii-chan!
ナイスバディだよ ちーちゃん！
Chisa-chan, really nice buddy!
千紗ちゃん すごいナイスバディ！
（観客）
おい すごいスタイルの子が
試合してるっぽいぞ
I heard there's a girl with a nice body!
Really? Where?
（観客）マジかよ どの子だ？
（伊織たち）千紗　千紗　千紗！
ナイスバディ！
Chisa! Chisa! Chisa! Nice buddy!
Stop!
やめてあげて！
Change of plan.
Let's destroy the slow one first.
作戦変更よ
まず あの鈍くさいほうを潰すわ
Okay.
了解
Game count, two-love!
（審判）ゲームカウント ツー･ラブ
ヒャッ！　うっ！
（部員）はあっ！
（愛菜）うわっ…
Are you okay?
（千紗）大丈夫？
Hey! That was dangerous!
おいおい
危ねえだろう オラ！
They're aiming for the body.
（耕平）あれは“ボディ狙い”だ
ん？　ボディ狙い？
Aiming for the body?
直接 相手の体をめがけて
打っていく戦術だ
It's when you aim for
the opponent's body.
I see.
なるほど
（千紗）ううっ！
（部員）うっ！
（耕平）おお 古手川のやつ
やり返したぞ！
Kotegawa paid them back.
She was aiming for their bodies too.
あれも ボディ狙いなのね
Good aim!
いい狙いだったよね
なるほど… それじゃあ
I see. Well, then...
千紗！　ナイスボディ！
（耕平）ナイスボディ！　古手川！
Chisa! Nice body!
Nice body, Kotegawa!
Chisa-chan, excellent nice body!
千紗ちゃん！
最高のナイスボディ！
（観客）おい どの子だよ
Which girl is it? Where is she?
Just stop!
本当にもう やめてあげて！
（ホイッスル）
Won by Tinkerbell!
ウォンバイ ティンカーベル！
（歓声）
What happened, Chisa?
どうしたんだ 千紗？
You kept holding your skirt down.
途中から
ウエアのすそばかり押さえて
I want to start the third match.
えー 第３試合を
始めたいと思うのですが…
Are you okay?
そこの君 大丈夫？
Where are your sweats?
（工藤）お前 ジャージは？
Don't worry about it.
お気になさらず
Being naked is his uniform.
こいつは裸がユニフォーム
みたいな男なんで
I was wondering how this would turn out.
（工藤）一時は
どうなるかと思ったが―
I'm going humiliate this guy.
こいつらをできるだけ
ぶざまに倒して…
ふっ！
（工藤）えっ？
（審判）フィフティーン･ラブ
Fifteen-love!
Here I go.
次 いきますよ
ぐっ！
（工藤）がっ…
（審判）サーティー･ラブ
Thirty-love!
I didn't know Iori was good at sports.
伊織って
スポーツ得意だったんだね
He had good control back there too.
そういや あいつ
あの時もコントロールよかったよな
Yeah. When he flipped up Chisa's skirt.
ああ 千紗ちゃんの
スカートめくったときか
（千紗）くっ…
You...
お前…
Leave it to me. Except for swimming!
水泳以外なら任せとけ
（部員）うう…
（工藤）調子に乗るなよ
Don't be so full of yourself.
Here we go!
（伊織）よっしゃ！
（工藤）この！
-Take that!
-You--
（伊織）甘いわ！
（部員）ぐっ！
（伊織）耕平！
（耕平）おう！
-Kohei!
-Okay!
おらあ！
Take that!
ああ…
Kitahara... They're pretty good.
北原… やつら 結構やるぞ
You're just too bad.
（伊織）
お前がやらなすぎるだけだ
（伊織）ぬううっ！
（工藤）ふっ！
とりゃあ！
（耕平）うわあっ！
（伊織）くっ！
（部員）ぬうっ！
（耕平）でやっ！
（工藤）くっ！
（耕平）わああ！
Game count, four-love!
（審判）ゲームカウント
フォー･ラブ
マズいぞ…
俺たちの力が 通じてない
This is bad!
This isn't working.
You're the one that's not working.
通じていないのは
お前だけだがな
Oh, yeah.
（工藤）ああ そうそう
I forgot to mention...
言い忘れたけど
うちのサークル―
Our club records matches
so we can study them later.
後学のために
試合は動画を撮ってるんだ
What?
（伊織･耕平）なんだって！
Hey, you bastards!
さては 貴様ら！
You just want to laugh at us when we lose!
俺たちの負けっぷり
さらして 笑う気だろ！
It's not about you losing...
いや 負けっぷりっつうかさ
We're already laughing about the way you're dressed.
その格好してる時点で
さらし者だろ
Kohei, it looks like it has come down to this.
（伊織）耕平
こうなったら もう…
I know.
（耕平）分かってるさ
もう 俺たちに残された手は…
We have no choice.
A KO!
（伊織･耕平）ＫＯしかない！
Are you guys plotting something?
お前ら なんか
不穏なこと考えてないか？
ハハハ… まさか そんなこと
Of course not.
Die!
死ねえ！
（部員）ヒャッ！
What was that shout?
（工藤）なんだ 今のかけ声は…
Nice, Kitahara! Nice serve!
（耕平）いいぞ 北原
ナイスサーブ！
All that's left is the fine adjustment.
（伊織）あとは 微調整だな…
どこがナイスサーブだ！
That's not a nice serve!
It didn't bounce, and it hit the fence!
ノーバンで
フェンスに当たってるだろ！
（伊織）おらあ！
（工藤）えっ？
（工藤）危ねえ！
（伊織）よけるな ひきょう者！
Look out!
Don't dodge, coward!
（工藤）
ひきょうなのは どっちだ！
Who's the coward?
Be careful.
If I dodge it, then I'm the one who gets the point.
（工藤）気をつけろよ
よけさえすれば
こっちの得点になるんだ
（部員）お… おう 分かってる
Yeah. I know.
ハッ！
No way!
（工藤）まさか！
（伊織）あうっ！
（工藤）うっ！
ううっ… くっ！
They're not letting their guard down.
ったく 油断も隙もないな
（部員）会長！
Captain!
これで手詰まりだろう
潔く負けを…
You've had enough, right? Just surrender.
You loser!
（耕平）この下手くそ！
やつかカメラのどっちかくらい
当ててみせろ！
I'm going to hit him or the camera!
Did we really have to play against them?
（部員）本当に あんなの
相手にする必要あったのか？
This is all your fault!
こうなりゃ なんでもいい
I don't care what happens now.
Just use one of your dirty tricks.
お前 得意の卑劣な手で
うまくやれや
なんで お前にそこまで
言われなきゃならんのだ… ん？
Look who's talking!
So you don't care what I do?
（伊織）どんな手でもいいのか？
（耕平）もちろんだ
Of course.
I see.
そうか…
Then I'm going to aim for a KO!
（耕平）狙いは？
（伊織）ＫＯだ
（耕平）よし！
それでこそ 北原だ
All right, that's my Kitahara!
はあっ！
（部員･工藤）は？
（伊織）命中
Bull's-eye!
お… お前
どういうつもりで…
What are you trying to...?
いやあ 不慮の事故で
欠員が出てしまいましたので―
We had an accident. Our player is out.
We can switch players, right?
メンバー交代でいいですよね
Is this where I come in?
（時田）おっと 出番か
（寿）俺もいけるが
I can play too!
（工藤･部員）ああ…
（衝撃音）
（工藤･部員）ギャア～！
（歓声）
4-6
VICTORY!
なんてことしやがる
クソ野郎！
Look what you did, you bastard!
（伊織）お前が どんな手でも
いいと言ったんだろうが！
You said you didn't care what I did!
To them, you idiot!
（耕平）それはあの連中に…
There's not an ounce of sportsmanship.
スポーツマンシップの
かけらもない…
Well, they won!
まあ 勝てたから
よかったんじゃない？
Iori is really good at tennis.
それにしても 伊織は
テニスうまかったねえ
Did you play in high school?
高校の頃 やってたの？
After the entrance exams were over.
受験が終わってからですけど…
You weren't in a club?
（愛菜）部活じゃないの？
（伊織）いやあ…
No...
I heard tennis was the best way
to get a girlfriend in college.
大学で彼女 作るには
テニスが一番と聞いて―
仲間たちと 特訓を
So I trained with my friends.
That's so shallow.
（時田）浅はかだな
（寿）考えが単純だ
You're so simple.
Are you okay with not joining the tennis club?
You trained so hard.
（梓）けど いいの？
そんなに特訓したのに
テニサーに入らなくて
It's okay.
（伊織）いいも何も
選択の余地がなかったもので
I didn't even have a chance to choose.
That's too bad.
それはかわいそうに
You have a tough life, Iori.
伊織も苦労しているなあ
What happened to your memory?
（伊織）あんたらの記憶は
どうなっているんですか…
Anyway, I'm done with tennis.
まあ でも
とりあえず テニスはいいです
Are you sure?
そうなの？
There's something else I want to do now.
（伊織）今は ほかに
やってみたいことができましたから
（時田）ふむ
（寿）そうかそうか
I see, I see.
（足音）
（伊織）うわっ
Thanks.
お疲れ
（伊織）おお…
Yeah.
And with that, we got the prize money.
（時田）というわけで
賞金も手に入れたことだし
Let's have an overnight trip!
合宿をしようかと思う
Our destination will be Okinawa!
なんと 場所は沖縄だ
-Okinawa?
（愛菜･千紗）沖縄!?
（耕平･伊織）マジですか!?
-Seriously?
お？
That's...
（伊織）あれは…
俺たちが見ていた 沖縄の雑誌
That's the magazine about Okinawa
we were looking at.
Did they do this for us?
もしかして 先輩
俺たちのために…
Okinawa. That's amazing.
沖縄とはすごいな
Yeah.
まったくだ
（寿と時田の笑い声）
HOW TO DRINK OKINAWAN LIQUOR
DEEP BLUE AL FINE
KAYA MIZUKI
Here's your mic, Kitahara.
（耕平）ほれ 北原 マイク
（伊織）俺もかよ
Me, too...? All right, let's do this!
よっしゃ いくぜ！
-Yeah, sing your heart out.
-You guys seem to be having fun.
（寿）おお～ 歌え歌え！
（時田）ノリノリだな
A fairytale whispers
In a fake world
♪～
Hiding in the complete darkness
I reach for the forbidden fruit
In my last days
Now I know the meaning of the song about hope
A broken gear will never stop again
Even if I were to lose everything
I'd still want you to know
Trapped in the sky so far away
I'm praying with ripped off wings
Because we span together
The vows of areppegio
If life sparkles only to the beat
of the resonating stars
I'll sacrifice everything
Till death do us apart
Cheers!
～♪
We now take a commercial break!
（一同）いったん
ＣＭでーす！
-So you were a bartender?
-Cool!
（千紗）バーテンやってたんですね
（愛菜）すごーい！
（マスター）君らも
やってみたらどうだい？
Why don't you try it too?
（梓）２人とも 似合ってるよ
It looks good on you two!
（耕平）うわあ！
目が！　目が！
My eyes! My eyes!
We have a naked relationship.
（寿･梓）裸の関係です！
NEXT EPISODE
"A MAN'S COCKTAIL"